SALEENA ANYA BAZ

FASHION COMMUNICATION STUDENT - NORTHUMBRIA UNIVERSITY

INFORMATION:

Name:

Saleena Anya Baz

Website:

Saleenaanya.com

@saleena.portfolio @ @saleenaanya **in**

EDUCATION:

BA (Hons) Fashion Communication Northumbria University

- Fashion Media and Communications.
- Media and Public Relations.
- Fashion Editorial and Journalism.
- Consumer Trend Research.

Newcastle College Sep 2015 - Jul 2017

 Level 3 Diploma in Fashion & Retail Enterprise.

HOBBIES/INTERESTS:

- Sketching/Painting
- Gym/Fitness
- Dance/Music
- Freelance Fashion Photgraphy & Styling.

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

- Adobe Photoshop CC
- Adobe In-Design
- Microsoft Office Suite

PERSONAL STATEMENT

An enthusiastic, ambitious professional with a strong work ethic and willingness to learn. Aspiring towards a career in brand management/ consultancy within creative arts & fashion. Currently in my final year studying BA (Hons) Fashion Communication at Northumbria University, alongside 5+ years of working in fashion retail. My skill set includes an excellency in PR & marketing, trend analysis, fashion editorial and journalism, photography, styling, Adobe Creative Suite and Microsoft Office.

CORE SKILLS

- Concept planning
- Adaptability
- Communication
- Creative
- Innovative
- Social media Management

- Organised
- Photography
- Research & Analysis
- Motivated
- Intuitive
- Determined

EXPERIENCE

Sales Advisor

The Dune Group

Newcastle Upon Tyne - 2015 - Present

- Daily Admin/Trade Reports.
- Driving in-store sales and delivering excellent customer service.
- Trend Analysis & Forecasting.
- Merchandising the shop floor and optimising stock selling.

Media Management/Photographer

Triple 555 Shisha Bar

Newcastle Upon Tyne -Jun 2018 - Aug 2019

- Managing all social media content for the company.
- Brand Promotion.
- Head of event design/curation.
- Event photography.

Campaign Developer

Fashion Revolution

Newcastle upon Tyne February 2019

- A collaborative project with Fashion Revolution to promote sustainability.
- Brand/clientele research.
- Producing original, innovative and creative solutions/outputs.
- Renewing and re-branding existing products to target a new audience.

Styling/Media Intern

The Boohoo Group - Manchester -July 2018

- Assiting in managment of social media/promotion.
- Assisting in styling/directing photoshoots.
- Showroom/cupboard assistance/stock merchandising.

REFERENCES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST